In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Wherever you are, you, evil spirits that are tormenting my people,
I say out, in the name of Jesus!
Out, in the name of Jesus!
You, evil spirit, out, in the name of Jesus!
Say out!
Out!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Prophet T.B. Joshua calls forward one of those who had manifested during the Mass Prayer for deliverance.
He stumbles and falls to the floor as he receives prayer in the power of the Holy Ghost.
I am Lucifer.
You are a Lucifer?
Yes, I am. I am not a Lucifer. I am Lucifer.
Can't you hear me? Come on.
The young man says he is Lucifer.
You said what?
How are you?
Oh, come on! Stop that!
Look at the legs!
Put your leg down!
Put it down!
Raise your hands!
Raise them up!
What?
Don't touch me! Please, don't touch me!
Stop that!
Please!
I'm begging you! Please!
Ah!
Gosh!
You did not have to do that!
Why are you tormenting me? Why?
You're tormenting me!
He's my body!
He's my temple!
I've come here to The Synagogue and you people have been tormenting me!
I only have business with him; I don't have with others.
The floor should start fighting you now!
Don't do that. Please!
You said what?
Watch your screen. This is Lucifer running away.
Leave him!
The ground should start fighting you!
See what is happening.
Now, the chair should start fighting you!
Chair, start fighting!
The ground, fight!
That is the downfall of Lucifer.
Where can you go from His presence?
He doesn't know that the ground is a messenger of God.
So, where can he run to?
If the ground needs my assistance, I will give my assistance.
So, we are not fighting ourselves.
He is a servant of God, and I am a servant of God.
The evil spirit who called himself Lucifer attempts to attack Prophet T.B. Joshua with the chair.
What happened?
Be on the floor!
Raise up your hands!
Close your eyes!
STANDARD FOR LIFE
My name is Adeleye Oluwasegun.
This is my dad, and this is my mum.
I'm a student. I'm studying biochemistry.
I'm in my final year, 400 level.
I belonged to a fellowship on campus.
We'd go out on village outreach and evangelism.
When we used to go, we'd pray and minister deliverance to people.
I was privileged to minister deliverance once and the demons inside him
manifested and I thought it was over.
After that, I started experiencing a lot of demonic attacks.
I started experiencing a lot of cobwebs.
Whenever I was in a prayer session and they mentioned the name Jesus,
I'd become very, very angry, violent and abusive.
There was an occasion that I went up to a person who was ministering
and I pulled him by the collar.
I wanted to kill him but the other brothers held me.
In the fellowship, we were being taught and our faith was built.
So, we essentially acted on that faith, though we were not anointed or ordained.
We read the Bible and it says that whosoever believes shall cast out demons.
We went in faith, casting out demons.
Thank you so much for delivering me.
We had been to so many places for this predicament until we came here.
Thank you so much.
Emmanuel! I'm free now.
My name is Adeleye Idowu and this is my wife, Wunmi Adeleye.
and this is my son, Segun Adeleye.
We sent him to university. He is in 400 level, as he said earlier on.
Some time last year September, we got a call from the school
that he had become a deliverance minister and started behaving strangely.
We were wondering because at my level where I am in the church of God,
I'm a Sunday school teacher and I know what it takes to be a deliverance minister.
Unless you are called and anointed, you cannot do it because we have different gifts from God.
Where God puts you, you have be content with it,
unless He asks you to move forward. That was why I was shocked.
When we came in contact with each other, I asked some questions
regarding what really happened.
It was then I learnt that they usually went out to deliver people.
I wondered if what he was doing was not above his capacity.
The first question I asked him,
'Do you have the power? Do you have the anointing?
Can you just do it anyhow you like it?'
The repercussions might be great.
Truly, Man of God, it was great.
Since that time, he had been possessed.
We had been to many places but all to no avail until we came here.
When we came here, he was delivered just like that.
I now know that the power of God really abides here and with the man of God.
Thank You, Jesus!
Hallelujah!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.